Florence is really a fool.
Because of her, our Agora day is extended.
You know, we should be supporting her.
I'm not saying we will not support her.
But does she have a realistic chance
against Camille?
With what we're about to do,
that girl will stand no chance.
We will ruin her.
We will destroy her.
I now present to you, Camille and Florence.
Do you think she is worthy
to be your Com Arts representative?
Bea?
Ooh.
Next.
Camille, that's not true.
I, for a fact, wanted to be her friend too.
But yesterday, I saw her.
I saw her making a fool of herself.
Is that the representative that you want?
Someone who is so messed up.
Oh my, she might mess up something
in the student body.
So, if you guys still don't believe
that I should be the Com Arts representative,
don't let the face
of one of the most dynamic departments
of this university
be someone with questionable morals.
She doesn't deserve
to be your representative.
She doesn't even deserve
to be in this school.
It's impossible that you saw her yesterday,
because we were together yesterday.
Why are you together? Do you even know her?
She's my girlfriend.
Oh my God...
You're kidding, right?
So, you're saying you know this woman,
and you're in a relationship?
So, are you saying the Ferells are liars?
Accusing us of lying is something our family
won't let you get away with it.
Because the Ferells are many things.
But to lie, we can't do that.
You know, that's enough.
Let's proceed to vote.
Camille, stop!
I hate her!
Why is she doing this to me?
Why is this happening?
What are you looking at?
Ms. Villarico, can I talk to you?
Dean?
Girlfriend, cook.
Tomatoes, tomatoes.
Potatoes, potatoes.
It seems there's not much difference.
What do you mean there's not much difference?
I mean, you cook for Nero,
you take care of him.
You live in his house
and you even went on a date on the farm.
Not to mention, if you get mad,
you burn down his bat cave.
Technically, it falls under
the definition of a girlfriend,
almost wife too.
Exactly. And to be fair,
I want what Nero did,
to call you his girlfriend instead of a cook.
It gives a huge dramatic effect. Imagine...
"We were together last night."
"Not because she's my girlfriend,
but because she's my cook."
Isn't that boring?
Well, yes,
and if you say she's a cook,
you have a lot of explaining to do.
Like... "why is she a cook?"
"Does she cook well?"
"She's still young.
Is she a cooking master boy?"
"Is she an anime character?"
Right?
At least, if you say she's my girlfriend,
they will easily get it.
Oh Lord, do rich people think this way?
They have defective minds.
And you, Nero, first thing tomorrow,
you'll take back everything you said.
Explain to them
that I am not your girlfriend.
I am your cook. I'm the cook of the Ferells.
No.
What do you mean "no"?
He can't do that, Florence.
If he does, he will lose his reputation.
Then, he shouldn't have done that.
They all lied just to ruin you.
And so?
We will lie too?
We will not tell the truth?
We will level with them
because they don't play fair?
It's more radical to be...
honest.
Okay, I'll be honest with you.
I won't follow what you want,
and you'll follow me.
From now on, act like my girlfriend.
And why would I do that?
You owe me three favors.
Three chances
that you will follow whatever I like.
No questions asked... no nothing.
So, three minus one, two more favors to go.
Come on, Florence,
being Nero's girlfriend
isn't the worst thing in the world.
There are far more worse things
in this world.
There's a war in Europe, global warming,
and income inequality.
Not to mention the rise of populism.
Manchester United, LA Lakers.
Exactly!
Will you stop bothering me?
But still, you have no choice.
Can I use one of your favors, Nero?
I'll just ask Florence
to do one of my assignments.
You know, as long as you ask properly,
I will help you with your assignment.
Wow, Bro, if she'll do your assignment,
then you'll end up owing her.
Of course.
Guys!
Something is happening.
It's better if you come back.
- Let's go.
- Okay, go.
Hello, hello.
Everyone, please settle down.
It has come to my attention that someone here
has photoshopped an image of another student
to spread malicious rumors
about another student.
If you read your student handbook,
which I'm sure you all did,
this is a clear violation of Chapter 7,
Section 3, and subsection C
that governs student conduct
here in our school.
We do not spread disinformation
to ruin our fellow Gyronellan.
No, no, no!
A big no!
So, in light of recent events,
we now declare Florence as the representative
of the Com Arts department.
Yes!
Thank you. Florence, care to join us?
No thanks, Grandfather Garp.
I'll eat with Ma'am Serafica.
Is it true that
you're the student representative of Com Arts?
Yes.
Are you happy?
Yes, I am so happy.
Are you happy that you're Nero's girlfriend?
I know everything. They told me about it.
Your day was eventful.
That's why you should teach them not to lie.
Oh, you're right. Alright.
It's true, we shouldn't tell a lie.
But you know, Florence, sometimes in life,
we have to compromise and improvise.
And you, Nero,
what you did is very admirable.
It's not the lying,
but it's your instinct to save Florence
from someone
who is destroying her character.
Florence here is family. She's one of us.
And it's our instinct to protect our own.
She's family and we always protect our own.
Hello, Mother. Hello, Father.
Everything is okay here.
We're happy because
you're adapting to your university.
It's a celebration!
A jubilation!
Congratulations, my child. Congra...
Wait, what did she win?
She's the head of her course.
Wow. You're now the head...
Congratulations on being
the head of your course.
What's her course?
It's Communication Arts.
You're something else.
Are you the father of our daughter?
Hey, Florence, you might become too busy
and forget about us.
Is that possible when you're my family?
Why, Florence, do you now
want a different family?
Are you transferring to a different family?
Mother is something else.
Of course not.
I'm just thinking,
I can't handle it if you're far from me,
and the challenges in the school,
if it weren't for the Ferells.
It's difficult to believe,
but as time goes by,
we're becoming a family too.
That's life, Florence.
As the world goes bigger,
more people will become part of our lives.
I am confident that there'll be more people
you can see as your family
because you have a good heart.
And they are slowly seeing
the goodness in you.
Florence,
since you're part of the Ferell family,
I hope they'll bequeath to you
even a bonsai plant.
- You're really a fool!
- Why?
I don't know about your father.
Father is something else.
Nero.
What do you need?
Don't hurt her.
She's a good person.
Why would I hurt Florence?
I know why you did that earlier.
You're trying to use Florence
to hurt Antonia.
I supported you
because you tried to protect Florence
from Camille.
But I hope you don't use her
to get the girl you really want.
First chance you get, you better cut it off.
Stop pretending that she's your girlfriend,
before someone gets hurt.
Your hair smells good.
You've been thinking a lot of nonsense,
that's why you're dreaming such things.
What's this? A dream within a dream?
Wake up, Florence. Wake up.
- Wake up!
- Florence.
What are you doing?
Why are you hurting yourself?
You're not true.
I won't be intimate with you.
Because I'm a good, good, girl
in a good, good, world.
And it's not a good, good thing
if you kiss me.
Florence, I'm just waking you up.
I've been knocking on your door.
It seems you overslept.
You're real! I'll just follow you.
I'll just follow.
I'll just follow!
- I'll just follow!
- Hurry up!
I slapped Nero.
Let's go?
Wait, I dreamt about this.
Is this still a dream?
Florence, we're late already.
Let's go.
- You go ahead.
- Florence, wait.
The reason why I waited for you
is so you won't be late.
So, let's go.
Do you want to play some music?
Go ahead.
I thought you don't want others
to touch your car?
That's okay, let's play some music.
Look, Florence.
The reason why I wanted to give you a ride,
is that I want to talk to you.
Owen is right.
I'm being unfair to you.
Owen?
He talked to me last night,
and warned me about you.
What for?
He saw my real intention,
and why I declared you to be my girlfriend.
Isn't it to debunk Camille's lies?
Well...
Are you telling me
that you have a different reason
why you became a knight in shining armor
during Agora day?
Yes.
It's a selfish reason.
What's the reason?
I want to get Antonia jealous.
Oh.
I see.
You can get mad, you can slap me, punch me,
or I'll get some of my things
and you can burn them again.
Nero...
thank you for your honesty.
And like what Grandfather Garp said,
we're like family.
So, if I can help you
achieve what your heart wants,
and that is,
for Antonia to realize how amazing you are
so she'll come back to you,
then I'm more than willing to help you.
Thank you, Florence.
Owen is right.
You're a good person.
Let's go?
Shall we, my Chummy Pie?
Florence, hi.
Hi, Antonia.
Nero, congratulations to you both.
You guys make such a cute couple.
Thank you.
The first time I met you,
I knew you were a good person.
To be honest,
I'm supporting you ever since
you stood up to Aira and Camille.
I've been hearing a lot of bad things
about them
and it took somebody like you
to reveal their true colors.
You're really lucky to have her, Nero.
So, you better take good care of her.
Anyway, I'll see you guys around.
Let's go.
It looks effective.
I saw a slight jealous moment
on Antonia's face.
That's good.
I hope she'll get jealous right away
and reconciles with Nero,
so we can end this fool's first favor.
And thank you, we'll go to the next favor.
But wait,
what if Antonia ignores the situation,
and Nero will use his other favors?
He'll kiss me in front of Antonia?
Oh no, not my virgin lips, please.
This is reserved for my future boyfriend.
My future real boyfriend
who will really love me.
But if this fool will court me...
Why not?
Should I be choosy?
Do you want to make it real
that we're in a relationship?
Oh my...
Does Nero have telepathic skills
that he can read my mind?
Does he want to kiss me?
You're holding my hand so tightly.
You can let go now.
No one... is looking.
How should I know?
Of course, I'm already immersed
in the role of your fake girlfriend.
Okay.
Is this the feeling of being used?
If I don't owe you any favor,
you're nothing to me.
Antonia.
What? You'll just let them be?
What do you mean?
I'm sure you're not stupid.
Do you really think
that Nero will just have
a new girlfriend overnight?
I'm not one to make silly assumptions
when it comes to other people.
The fact is, Nero and I are over.
So, he can do whatever he wants.
If there's something that bothers me,
that's you.
Me?
Why are you telling me this?
I thought you'd be interested
to know the real score
between Nero and Florence.
And I thought you're interested to know
that all of this is just an act.
Well, thank you for the information, Owen,
but it doesn't take a genius
to realize what Nero is doing.
He's simply protecting Florence
when Aira and Camille
were destroying her reputation.
But what I don't understand is...
why are you guys protecting her?
Who is she in your lives?
She's our cook.
Cook?
Yes.
Not any ordinary cook.
She's the cook
who changed everything in the mansion.
What do you mean?
Well, ordinarily,
no one stays long in the mansion
no matter how good they are.
You know us Ferells.
But when she came, she changed everything.
He still can't get it.
What do you call a group of dogs?
- What?
- Aso-ciation.
- That's possible.
- Nice. Nice.
Tough crowd. Tough crowd.
One more. Knock-knock.
Who's there?
A lot of men.
She's special.
She makes you see things differently.
She can show that the world is colorful.
She's not afraid to show her heart.
She makes you hopeful.
She makes you brave.
Brave enough that you can be happy.
And she makes you understand
that to be happy...
you have
to embrace it, grab it, and choose it.
And when the opportunity comes,
you shouldn't be scared.
Are you telling me all this...
because you want me to break them apart?
You want me to go back to Nero
so they can stop pretending.
Because you're the one who likes Florence.
You're the one who really likes her.
And you're jealous because
Nero is playing the role of the boyfriend,
the role that you wish
you could be playing instead.
I thought you don't like making assumptions
about other people.
You're right.
I'm not one to make assumptions,
but what I can only say to you
is be careful, Owen.
This is a dangerous playground
that you're in.
And it looks like you and Nero
are about to be involved
in a seriously complicated situation.
Florence, hi.
Hello.
Hello to our Com Arts representative,
by the way, they are the representatives
of the different sections of Com Arts.
And we are all here today
for our first departmental consultation.
I thought no one will come
but it's a good thing
that we're all here right now.
Of course, Ms. Florence.
Oh, don't call me Miss.
Let's not be too formal.
We're all students here, and we all fart.
There you go. Of course, speaking of plans...
Yes, I have plans.
Actually, I have a lot of plans.
Because based on my observation
in this university these past few days,
I have some ideas
that I want to share with you
so that our student life can be improved.
First, I saw the hangout area
of GU Com Arts Club
and it needs a lot of improvement.
That's why I will ask for a budget
from the student council
so we renovate it.
And I also want to apply
Google's work-life balance environment
to the department.
In our case, school-life balance.
I also thought of an anti-bullying platform
because it's a rampant problem in GU.
So I'll ask IT College to create
a direct messaging app
so that the anonymous students
can file reports and harassment
so we can investigate it.
And I also have plans to revive our Book Club
so we, the students,
can have personal interaction
and rediscover the jewel of GU
which is our library.
Are there any problems with my ideas?
Are there things you don't like,
or do you want to add something?
It's okay, Florence.
Your ideas are good,
but it seems that's not what we're expecting
to talk about in this meeting.
Why? What should we talk about?
- About the Grand GU Ball.
- Yes.
Grand GU Ball?
Weren't you informed, Florence?
It's the most important event
here in GU, right?
And it's coming up already.
So as our student representative,
I think it's a good idea
that we should all brainstorm
for this upcoming event.
I'm sorry, Florence,
but the Grand GU Ball is not just a party.
Yes, and this year is very important.
That's because the Com Arts are
the designated host of this grand event.
Well... If that's how important it is,
the floor is now open for suggestions.
Do you have ideas?
Why don't we make a localized version
of Coachella?
Let's call it a music festival
so it wouldn't be too boring ball
and not always formal.
Bad idea. I mean, it's so hot in our country.
We'll smell like onions.
Besides, after Astroworld,
I don't think it's a good idea.
Let's go for something vintage.
A Retro Ball.
No way. It smells like the nostalgia
of grandmother and grandfather.
As for me, I suggest
that we go for "classic eleganza",
like the 1800s Victorian Party.
It's so hard to dance
with a full skirt and petticoat.
I have a better one.
Why not let's just make a Filipino version
of "Le Bal"?
That's going to be a show-off.
Do you want to show off?
How about our own version
of the famous Il Ballo del Doge?
Yes, and let's have Pierre Gagnaire's
fusion cuisine.
I love his foie gras soup with lentil gnocci
and balsamic onions.
Or the dish inspired
by that Chinese French Artist.
The Zao Wou Ki.
- That's it.
- Yes.
The beet and orange-infused daikon
with onion puree.
That's okay,
as long as the wine is Romaneè-Conti.
Perfecto.
Let's go.
All your suggestions are good.
I'll think about it and study all of them.
I'll make sure to integrate
all your suggestions.
Let's go.
Florence, wait, wait, wait.
You left something.
Your hair, it's so long.
- Lina.
- It might get tangled.
- Bye.
So, how's your student consultation?
What?
Is this included in our pretend relationship?
Pretend that you're concerned
with what happened with my day?
You know, no need.
I know you're not interested
in what's happening in my life.
There's no difference if lightning strikes me
or the crocodiles will eat me up.
We're just pretending
so we should mind our own business
and I know that.
I'm sorry.
You're asking nicely,
and I answered you with those things.
I don't know why I answered you that way.
Maybe I'm just pressured
with being the student representative.
Think about it,
I thought of a lot of ideas and projects
to make our university better,
but then all they want to talk about
is just one thing,
the Grand GU Ball.
What hurts the most,
I don't understand anything
about what they're talking about.
They're like aliens with alien tongues.
What's that,
Coachella, Astroworld, Le Bal...
Il Ballo del... Doge?
That's it.
And there's something more.
They're talking about that Pierre Gagnaire
as if it's their neighbor
when I don't even know who that is.
I don't have any idea.
Who is that?
Maybe this is my karma.
I'm acting like a smart alec.
Coachella is a popular music festival.
Coachella Valley Music and Arts Festival
that is held in California.
Maybe that's why they also said Astroworld,
because that's a perfect example of
a music festival that didn't go well.
A stampede can happen,
or people can get hurt,
like what happened in Astroworld.
Le Bal is short for Le Bal des Debutantse.
That was formally known as Crillon Ball,
which happens every year in France.
It's like the Filipino debut party,
and the children of famous
and well-known people are invited.
The Il Ballo del Doge is a masquerade ball
that is held in Venetian Palace
that is called Palazzo Pisani Moretta
in the Grand Canal.
So, I assume that's the grand canal
in Venice, Italy, right?
Because with the tone of your voice,
it's impossible that it's just the canals
around the area
or Mall of Taguig or whatever city.
Whatever they call the canal there.
Exactly.
And Pierre Gagnaire is a famous chef.
But if you'll ask me, he is overrated.
I think you're a better cook compared to him.
Thank you for your vote of confidence.
If there's something you don't understand
in this world,
don't hesitate to ask me.
That's the least I can do.
Thank you.
It's still early.
Let's eat first.
Huh? Where?
Thank you.
Here, Ma'am.
Go ahead and order.
Soup?
450 pesos per bowl?
What's that?
Do the ingredients have gold dust?
Why is it so expensive?
Just order, and I will pay for it.
I can't help but look at the price.
It makes me feel guilty to eat...
Oh my... Pork adobo, 1,000 pesos per order?
That's already good for 10 people.
Florence, I'm hungry, okay?
Stop overreacting. I'll pay for it.
Overreacting, Nero? Me?
They're overpriced.
No!
This is very wrong.
Very, very, very, very, wrong.
And besides, I'm not your real girlfriend
for you to spend on me this much.
You should spend it on your real girlfriend.
You should invest in her, not me.
Well, even if I become
your real girlfriend...
I still can't eat in a place like this, Nero.
This is a luxury, Nero.
And besides, there are a lot of
cheap eateries in the area
that are delicious.
So, if you want to eat, go ahead.
I will not eat here.
Whatever is left, I'll donate to charity.
Okay fine,
where is this place accepted
by your moral standards?
That's it.
That's the food that you can eat
without your conscience bothering you,
unlike the place you brought me earlier.
I think they're scammers.
They charge you so much.
They're higher than our electricity bill.
Hey, remember you asked me earlier
where I want to eat?
Well, this is it.
We're here.
Promise, Nero, it's delicious.
Just try it.
First, Barbecue.
It's delicious.
This is one of my favorites here.
- Come on, try it.
- I don't eat that.
You're such a killjoy.
Nero, I know that you're a rich kid,
but you should also try this kind of food.
Come on.
I told you I don't eat that.
Well, you're nothing.
I thought you eat food like this
since you grew up in a barrio.
It turns out I'm wrong.
Mister, give me one isaw,
betamax, and chicken ass.
What happened?
I thought you don't eat food like this?
Did you get hungry?
You were forced?
I don't eat barbecue,
but I eat isaw, betamax, and chicken ass.
Those are my favorite.
That's our usual food
on the medical mission with dad.
Wow, in fairness,
you've memorized all the names.
To be fair, I wasn't expecting that.
You're an expert
when it comes to grilling food.
Are you smiling?
He's more cowboy than me.
So, his favorite fruit is rambutan.
And it looks like his favorite food
is grilled stuff in Hepa Lane.
Good job, Florencia,
you're slowly solving Nero's mysterious side.
Come on, you can ride with me to school.
Let's go, Florence.
Bro, I will bring Florence to school.
I will.
I'm the boyfriend.
Do you mean fake boyfriend?
I understand you're trying
to protect Florence,
but this is getting ridiculous.
Florence and I have an agreement.
She agreed to help me, so don't meddle.
- Dad!
- Wait, you shouldn't hurt her.
He's my father.
Still, Camille,
even if he's your father,
he doesn't have a right to hurt you that way.
Hey you, don't meddle.
This is a family matter.
There's trouble in Camille's school.
I had a confrontation
with the grandsons of Don Ferell.
A Ferell woman started it.
A Ferell woman?
What's that?
Do you want to find out?
There are lights too.
Why do you have a comforter?
Well, just spread it out.
Lie down. I said lie down.
Are you ready?
- What?
- Are you ready?
I'll count to three...
One, two, three..
- You're rude!
- Hey, what's that?